<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyKelompok</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Universitas Handayani Makassar</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">kelompoksatu.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>

    <string-array name="spinner_array">
        <item>--Pilih--</item>
        <item>Iphone</item>
        <item>Oppo</item>
        <item>Samsung</item>
        <item>Nokia</item>
        <item>Xiomi</item>
        <item>Blackberry</item>
        <item>Motorola</item>
        <item>Experia</item>
        <item>Vivo</item>
        <item>Realme</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="random_text_1">
        Hadoop is a data processing tool used to process large size data over distributed
        commodity hardware. The trend of Big Data Hadoop market is on the boom and it’s
        not showing any kind of deceleration in its growth. Today, industries are capable
        of storing all the data generated at their business at an affordable price just
        because of Hadoop. Hadoop helps the industry to know their customer’s behavior,
        customers buying priorities i.e. what they loved the most, and click patterns,
        etc. Hadoop provides personalized recommendations and personalizes ad targeting
        features. Companies are generating thousands of petabytes of data every day so the
        demand for Big Data professionals is very high. Even after a few years, Hadoop will
        be considered as the must-learn skill for the data-scientist and Big Data Technology.
        Companies are investing big in it and it will become an in-demand skill in the future.
        Hadoop provides personalized recommendations and personalizes ad targeting features.
        Companies are generating thousands of petabytes of data every day so the demand for Big
        Data professionals is very high. Even after a few years, Hadoop will be considered as
        the must-learn skill for the data-scientist and Big Data Technology. Companies are
        investing big in it and it will become an in-demand skill in the future.
    </string>

    <string name="random_text_2">
        Humans are coming closer to the internet at a very fast rate. It means that the
        volume of data Industries is gathering will increase as time passes because of more
        users. Industry’s are gradually analyzing the need for this useful information they
        are getting from their users. It is for sure that the data always tends to an increasing
        pattern so the company’s are eventually acquiring professionals skilled with Big Data
        Technologies. According to NASSCOM, India’s Big Data Market will reach 16 billion USD by
        2025 from 2 billion USD. The growth of smart devices in India is growing at a very huge
        rate that will cause growth in theBig Data Market. Since Big Data is growing the demand
        for Big Data professionals will be high.  Hadoop provides personalized recommendations and
        personalizes ad targeting features. Companies are generating thousands of petabytes of data
        every day so the demand for Big Data professionals is very high. Even after a few years,
        Hadoop will be considered as the must-learn skill for the data-scientist and Big Data
        Technology. Companies are investing big in it and it will become an in-demand skill in the future.
    </string>
</resources>

